[SAD]😢 You are made to be ruled in the end. It will be
[SAD]😢 every man for himself. What do we do? We get
ready. There
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 [SAD]😢 was an idea to bring together a
remarkable people. So when we
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 [SAD]😢 needed them, they could fight the
battles that we never could. Gentlemen,
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 [SAD]😢 what are you prepared to do? No
offense, but I don't play
well with others. Big man and suit armor. Take that
away, what
[SAD]😢 are you?
[LAUGHTER]😂 [SAD]😢 A genius billionaire playboy
philanthropist. If we can't protect the Earth, I'm
[LAUGHTER]😂 [SAD]😢 sure we'll event it. Dr. Banner, your
work is unparalleled and I'm
a huge fan of the way you lose control and turn into
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 an enormous green range monster.
Thanks.